#### Contact

jgoachee@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jannagoachee (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Consulting

Management Consulting

Healthcare Information Technology

#### Languages

Spanish

#### Certifications

**ACLS** 

**CCRN** 

Green Belt

BLS

**NIH Stroke** 

#### Honors-Awards

Doyle Award Finalist Doyle Award Finalist

# Janna Goachee MPA, RN

Director, Population Health Operations at VillageMD Greater Atlanta Area

# Summary

Registered Nurse and highly driven leader with experience in leading large scale program development, continuous quality improvement, strategic planning and systems analysis. Advanced understanding of population health, hospital operations, post-acute sector and care coordination models. Goal oriented with demonstrated ability to build and lead teams to quantifiable success based on organizational goals.

# Experience

VillageMD
Director, Population Health Operations
November 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)
Georgia

VillageMDis a leading provider of primary care management services for healthcare organizations moving toward a primary care-led, high-value clinical model. The VillageMD solution provides data analytics, a physician-based care coordination model, and on-the-ground support resources to make improvements at the point of care, resulting in high quality clinical outcomes for all patients. VillageMD also provides access to value-based reimbursement contracts that reward physicians for delivering high quality, cost effective care. VillageMD works with physician groups, independent practice associations, and health systems to improve quality, deliver a first-rate patient experience, and lower total medical costs in the communities they serve.

JLG Health Solutions
Business Owner
June 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)
Greater New York City Area

Mount Sinai Health System 4 years 5 months

Director for Care Standardization and Integrative Care 2017 - November 2018 (1 year)

Page 1 of 3

Clinical Program Director, Clinical Integration & Care Transitions January 2015 - November 2017 (2 years 11 months)

New York, New York

Project Management Intern
July 2014 - December 2014 (6 months)

Greater New York City Area

New York Presbyterian Hospital
Clinical Nurse
May 2012 - May 2017 (5 years 1 month)
NSICU, CSICU, MICU, CCU, SICU

- Areas of practice: NSICU, CSICU, CCU, MICU, SICU
- Develop holistic plans of care for patients in collaboration with interdisciplinary team and delegate interventions as appropriate to ensure patient safety and improve patient outcomes
- Complete audits related to patient care outcomes and patient safety
- Created and delivered formal continuing education (CE) accredited training programs for staff, that resulted in reduction of pressure ulcer occurrence and CAUTI rates
- Developed and implemented multiple quality improvement projects aimed to improve patient care based on evidence based practice models as part of the quality improvement council

Shands at the University of Florida Registered Nurse June 2010 - April 2012 (1 year 11 months)

- Served on multiple quality improvement councils, including Documentation
   Legal, Clinical Outcomes, and Patient Safety, that developed strategies to
   improve provider documentation, patient outcomes, and quality of care delivery
- Selected to act as Epic Super User in implementation of Epic Electronic Health Record hospital wide
- Participated in the development and implementation of the Patient Mobility Enhancement Project, resulting in a decrease in length of stay specifically for the neurological trauma patient population

Munroe Regional Medical Center Nurse Intern March 2009 - May 2010 (1 year 3 months) Obtained clinical experience in a 32 bed ICU, 52 bed Cardiology Unit, Medical Telemetry, and Maternity. Provided holistic client care and assisted nurses and other members of the healthcare team in performing various interventions to improve clients health. Obtained experience in performing nursing skills, as well as enhancement of critical thinking skills and application, participated in multiple rapid response codes.

## Education

New York University

Masters of Public Administration, Healthcare Policy and Financial Management · (2013 - 2015)

UCLA Anderson School of Management

Certificate, Global Entrepreneurship · (2018 - 2018)

University of Southern California

Certificate, Project, Operations and Supply Chain Management · (2018)

University of Central Florida

BS, Nursing · (2010 - 2011)

**Duke University** 

Population Care Coordinator Program · (2017)